(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Pamela always gets pimples at the worst time.
She once had a pimple during her birthday
party.
She once had a pimple when she had
to make a speech.
She once had a pimple on her first
date.
Pamela expected that she would get a pimple
on prom.
Prom is a special dance for high school
students.
Girls wear pretty dresses and heels.
Guys wear fancy suits and ties.
Pamela wanted everything to go perfectly.
She made sure she would not get any
pimples.
She ate healthily.
She drank lots of water.
She used lotion constantly.
She used pimple cream too.
On prom day, she looked at the mirror.
Her face was clear.
It was the first time she had clear
skin on a special day.